人人影視
YYeTs.com
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
翻譯： 暴龍蛋     圈圈     阿髻     胖兔純
翻譯： 蘇小黛     Kiko     DustD
時間軸： 濃子   萌    校對： 蘇小黛   胖兔純
后期： 孤帆    總監： 米小勒   胖兔純
塞勒姆
第一季  第五集
《塞勒姆》前情提要
Previously on "Salem"...
-你是否曾想過  -什么
- Do you ever wonder? - What?
或許我們可以離開這里
If we could leave this place?
格里安娜  你不能待在這里
Gloriana, you mustn't be here.
在上帝的處所
What will you do here --
你能怎么樣
in the house of the lord?
你來這里做什么  霍克
What the hell are you doing here, Hooke?
小心點  上尉  除非你不介意
Now, careful, captain... unless you do not mind me
我告訴塞勒姆的人們
telling the good people of salem
約翰·奧登到底是個什么樣的人
just who john alden really is.
半夜包裹就是你的了
The package shall be yours by midnight.
靈獸從她身上脫離了
The familiar has been cut from her.
怎么會
How?
通過驅魔術
An exorcism...
毫無疑問是她的傻瓜父親干的
performed by her dolt of a father, no doubt.
我們必須用新的代替
So we must replace it.
天哪
My god.
那個女孩只是因為身體狀況而日趨虛弱
The girl has been rendered frail by her circumstance.
她只是需要休息一段時間
She needs but a moment of rest.
之后  她就會恢復力量
After which, she will again be strong enough
去指認他人
to point the finger.
張嘴吧
Open your mouth.
我知道你是什么東西
I know what you are.
讓他們進房間里去干  好嗎
Get 'em into a room, will ya?
我馬上就回來
I'll be back in two shakes.
你要去哪
You're leaving?
你聾了啊  女兒
Are you deaf, girl?
給他們找個房間
Get 'em into a room!
好的  媽咪
Yes, mum.
知道我們為什么召喚你過來嗎
我不知道
I do not.
是為了約翰·奧登
Yo'a'nes John Alden.
約翰·奧登
John Alden.
他怎么了
Yes?
他干擾了我們的大祭典  瑪麗·西布里
你得去幫我們解決
遵命
Yes. Yes.
昨晚奧登為了保住秘密殺了一個叫霍克的男人
那肯定是他不愿讓瑪麗·西布里知道的秘密
你必須查出真相并利用它把奧登逐出塞勒姆
但你不是說知道秘密的人已經死了嗎
Yet, you say the man who holds the secret is dead.
我們中有人精通巫師的黑魔法
憑她一己之力就能讓死者說話
確定我們可以相信她嗎
Are we certain we can trust her?
我們別無選擇
我不確定這個仆人是否忠心
I'm not so sure the servant is loyal.
我曾經覺得你的倔強是個優點
I used to think your stubbornness a virtue.
你現在不覺得了嗎
And you don't any longer?
現在外面風聲鶴唳  你為何還要只身前往呢
Why go alone when there is influence in numbers?
那姑娘知道真相了
The girl has shown her color.
但還不至于威脅到我們
We are well beyond the point of intimidation.
也許我們已經有被鏟除的危險了呢
Then perhaps we are at the point of elimination.
或許吧  但只是暫時的
Perhaps, but for the time being,
她活著遠比死了有價值
She is worth much more to us alive than dead.
*擂我戰鼓*
*Pound me the witch drums*
*鼓鳴震天*
*Witch drums*
*擂我戰鼓*
*Pound me the witch drums*
*鼓鳴震天*
*The witch drums*
*寧入地獄*
*Better pray for hell*
*不留人間*
*Not hallelujah*
看看誰來了 梅西  西布里夫人
Look who's here, Mercy. Mrs.Sibley.
-坐起來  -你先出去吧
-Sit up straight, girl. - Leave us.
你先出去  牧師
Leave us, reverend.
好的
Yes.
遵命
Certainly.
你昨晚來找過我
You came to visit me last night.
有嗎
Did I?
不用再裝了
The time for coyness has passed.
很明顯  你很清楚我的身份
It is clear you know exactly who and what I am.
唯一的問題是
The only question that remains
你會怎么做
is what you will do with that information.
那取決于你  西布里夫人
That depends on you, Mrs. Sibley.
你想怎樣  小姑娘
What do you want, girl?
我想要你停止
I want it to stop...
那些痛苦與折磨
the torture, the torment, the suffering.
否則我就會說出去
Or I will tell them.
我會告訴大家你的真實身份
I will tell them all who and what you are.
你根本對我一無所知
You know nothing of me...
你不知道我做了什么  放棄了什么
or what I've done or given up
經歷了什么才變成今天的樣子
or endured to be who I am.
你受刑是因為你反抗
You are tortured because you resist.
屈服于我  你就會體驗到其中的樂趣
Give in to me, and you will know only pleasure.
你折磨我
You torture me.
你把那條蛇放進了我身體里
You put the snake inside of me.
你就是那個咬我肩膀的女巫
You are the hag that bites my shoulder.
說話小心點  否則你的愚蠢
Careful, or your foolishness
會讓你的價值相形見絀
will come to overshadow your usefulness.
你之所以還活著
You live still...
是因為我允許你活著
because I allow it.
你還能呼吸是因為我想讓你呼吸
You breathe only because I wish it.
你會殺我嗎
You would kill me?
如果你亂說的話
If you speak.
保持沉默  你就能活下去
Stay silent, and you shall live.
我深不可測  內心豐盈
My heart is deep and full.
我很想再給你一次機會讓你證明自己的價值
It yearns to give you further chance to prove your worth.
讓我失望  就是讓你自己失望
Fail me, and you fail yourself.
拋尸山壑等待你的最終決定
The crag awaits your decision.
該死
Damn it.
你找我嗎
You sent for me?
對
Yes.
如果你想再次羞辱我
If your purpose is further humiliation
或想繼續探尋心靈
or probings of the heart,
我已經受夠了
I, for one, have had my fill.
我想給你個建議
My purpose is a proposition.
其實是想跟你做筆買賣
A business arrangement of sorts.
你說
I'm listening.
你告訴我
In which you would tell me
你一周最多能賺多少錢
the sum of your most fruitful week's bounty,
我永久性地給你雙倍的錢
and I shall provide double in perpetuity...
你來陪我
for your company...
把你寶貴的時間給我
and your precious time...
只給我一個人
in exclusivity.
你想徹底把我買下來
So you wish to buy me outright.
我是家里的獨子
I'm an only child.
我不喜歡與人分享
I never learned to share.
你這是向我道歉嗎
Which is as close as a man like you comes to an apology.
你看到我跟其他人在一起
Was it really so very painful for you
真的很痛苦嗎
to see me with another?
真的
Yes.
你愿意成為我的人嗎
Will you be mine?
柯頓
Cotton.
奧登上尉
Captain Alden!
你怎么來了
What brings you here?
因為這個
This.
你確定嗎  多蒂
Are you sure, Dottie?
你確定她不會傷害我們
Are you sure she won't hurt us?
她肯定不會傷害我們的...
'Course she won't hurt us...
除非你是個巫師
...unless you be a witch.
你好  梅西
Hello, Mercy.
我們可以進去嗎
May we come in?
他們會到你屋里找你嗎  梅西
They come to you in your room, Mercy?
他們...
Them...
巫師
witches?
有時吧
Sometimes...
有時候會在其他地方
And other times in other places.
他們現在在這里嗎
Are they here with us now?
現在你能看到他們嗎
Can you see them as we speak?
不  他們現在不在
No, I don't see them now.
他們會傷害你嗎
Do they hurt you?
有時候會
Sometimes.
那是種什么感覺
What's it like?
什么什么感覺
伸手指認別人
To point your finger
讓別人膽戰心驚
and make them shake and tremble with fear.
指認別人  看著他們逃跑
To point your finger and watch them run.
不  不是那樣的
No, it's not like that...
根本不是
at all.
我發誓
I swear.
塞勒姆沒有哪個女人能有那種權力
No woman in Salem has ever had that kind of power.
連瑪麗·西布里都沒有
Not even Mary Sibley.
你們是說我...
You think I have sway...
在塞勒姆民眾之中有支配力量
...amongst all the people of Salem?
你手指所向便關乎生死
Your little finger points to life a-and death itself.
告訴我們  巫師是什么樣子
Tell us... what do the witches look like?
還有件事  西布里夫人
One more thing, Mrs. Sibley...
碼頭有大量包裹
There was an overflow of parcels left on the britania,
都應該交給一個叫威廉·霍克的人
all of which are to be delivered to a William Hooke.
我們四處都找遍了
Now, we've looked high and low.
但是沒人知道他的行蹤
No one could seem to locate the fellow.
知道了  我會處理的
I see. I'll take care of it.
謝謝您  夫人
Thank you, madam.
他們不會找到霍克先生的  永遠不會
They will not find Mr. Hooke... not now, not ever.
我不會過問他的情況
I won't ask what happened to him.
你也不該過問
Nor should you.
那就保守秘密  免得有人起疑心
Then contain it before curiosity grows.
西布里夫人  下午好
Uh, Mrs. Sibley, uh, good afternoon.
能麻煩她跟我走一趟嗎
Might I borrow your girl?
我家夫人吃了有問題的貽貝  病得厲害
The missus has taken ill with a batch of wayward mussels
想要她特制的藥劑來一緩病痛
and now begs relief with one of her exceptional tonics.
請向霍爾夫人致以我最迫切的問候
Please send Mrs. Hale my most urgent regrets.
您有心了
Most kind.
理查茲先生  請把這位霍克先生
Oh, Mr. Richards, uh, fetch for me a list of items
要收取的貨物清單給我一份
this Mr. Hooke was here to receive,
記載了貨物來源地的那一份
one that also perhaps includes their site of origin.
這就去辦  夫人
Right away, madam.
你的謊話太拙劣了
Your lie is clumsy.
沒人生病
No one is ill.
小姐跟我一樣清楚這一點
My mistress can see that as clearly as I.
是的 說到謊言和花招
Yes, well, when it comes to lies and subterfuge,
我得佩服你的本事
I defer to your expert endowments.
說出你的目標  不然我就走了
State your purpose or be gone with you.
我的目標是把約翰·奧登逐出塞勒姆
My purpose is to rid this town of John Alden
一勞永逸
once and for all,
除非你對這個目標不感興趣
unless that is a purpose for which you lack interest.
這是同一個姑娘
That was the same girl...
在蘭姆
from Lamb's,
被你打過一拳的那個
the one you threw a punch over.
是嗎
Was it?
我不知道她們還出門待客呢
Wasn't aware they made outcalls.
把那些畫面再跟我描述一次
Tell me again of the visions.
泛黃的面孔
Yellowed faces...
身體布滿了皮疹和水皰
bodies overcome by rash and blister...
許多人死去
death in great numbers.
是把這個物件拿出來的時候看見的嗎
And this came to you as the artifact was brought to life?
是的
Yep.
你說這東西是從哪兒來的
Where did you say it came from?
鎮子里所有東西的來源  船只
Where everything in this town comes from... a ship.
"偉大的儀式"
Ritum Magni.
大祭典
The grand rite?
我們所了解的只來自傳說  流言  神話
Most of what we know is lore... rumor, legend.
這里提到了這個物件 "惡靈"
It says this object, this "Malum,"
在歷史上
has thought to be present
每次大祭典中都會出現
at every grand rite throughout history.
我看過的資料顯示
Everything I have read has said that the grand rite
大祭典的嘗試從未成功過
has only ever been attempted, never completed.
或許瘟疫只是祭典的一部分
Maybe plague's only part of it.
這是邪惡之物
This object is evil.
它為惡魔回歸祝圣
It consecrates the earth for the devil's return.
它是被寄送過來的  本該有人接收
It was here for delivery. Someone was expecting it.
一個巫師
A witch.
我們必須立刻通知行政委員們
We must inform the selectmen immediately.
不行
No.
為什么不
No?
我們有巫師想要的東西
We have something the witches want.
沒什么比這個更能吸引他們的注意
What better way to get their attention?
沒什么比這個更能讓你送命
What better way to get yourself killed?
我們都身處險境
We are all in danger,
但我寧可死去
but I would rather die
也不要落入塞勒姆的異徒手中
before Salem's finest control my fate.
你跟我一起嗎
Are you with me?
不在那邊  你這可恨的怪胎
Not over there, you infernal mutant!
在這邊
Over here!
就是他
That's him.
治安官把你帶走的真正目的是什么
And the magistrate's true purpose in taking you from me?
眼見為實
My eyes betrayed my sense
霍爾夫人確實病得打翻了便壺
when I came upon Mrs. Hale bent over her chamber pot.
如果你堅持要圓這個謊
If you insist upon this lie,
我就不得不問一句了
it forces me to ask
你現在如此匆忙離開又是要去哪兒
where you're off to now with such great urgency.
藥店
The apotek.
我手頭的珀希鼠李樹皮不多了
I run low on the bark of cascara sagrada.
當然了
By all means.
這就像教皇偉大的長袍
It's like the great flowing robe of the pope.
或者是國王鑲滿珠寶的王冠
Or the jeweled-up crown of a king.
這個要討厭得多  我敢保證
Well, it's quite disagreeable on -- I assure you.
想想看
Just think of it...
被英俊的麥哲牧師
being led through the market
指引著穿過集市
by the handsome reverend Mather.
他是什么樣的  梅西
What's he like, Mercy, hmm?
他會談到上帝和魔鬼嗎
Does he speak of God and demons?
我們聊過很多次
We've spoke many times.
他對我的遭遇很感興趣
He's shown great interest in my affliction.
是你伸出了手指
It's you who points the finger...
整個塞勒姆屏息以待
while all of Salem holds their breath and waits.
也不完全是那樣  我...
Well, it's not exactly like that. I...
如果我有你的本事  我知道自己該控訴誰
If I had your say-so, I know who I'd accuse.
誰
Who?
她父親
It's her father.
她會指控自己的父親
She'd accuse her own father.
為什么
Why?
他成天逼她在大街上賣唱
Makes her sing in the streets all day long
而自己則在蘭姆的酒館里買醉
while he nurses the bottle at Lamb's --
賣唱  乞討
Sing and beg.
然后他將她賺來的錢全數拿去買酒
Then he takes what coin she's made for spirits
稍有不如意還對她拳腳相加
and beats her senseless for her troubles.
這是真的嗎
Is this true?
下個月我就滿十五歲了
I'm to be 15 next month,
他說到時候就要將我賣去妓院
and he swears to sell me to the Rod.
你父親要將你賣去妓院
Your father means to sell you to the whorehouse?
我要逃離這里
I'll run away.
就算他賣了我  我...  我要逃走
Even if he sells me, I'm -- I'll run.
我不會允許這種事發生
No one is running away.
決不允許
No one.
梅西
罪人還是救世主
Sinner or savior!
我們該如何辨別
How are we to know?!
看看那些被詛咒者所受的折磨
Look but to the torment of the damned,
好好想想天使與惡魔之間的區別
and think well of the difference betwixt angels and devils,
你就知道何為罪惡及其根源
and you will know what sin is and where sin resides!
你就別再繼續煽動大家的情緒了行嗎
How 'bout you not rile the crowd further than they are?
25美分一張
It's two bits a sheet.
我這還多著呢  除非你想把它們都買了
I'm still full up here, unless you'd like to buy me out.
不如直接揍你一頓更省事
Be loads more fun to beat you stupid.
霍爾小姐
Miss Hale.
奧登上尉
Captain Alden.
真是美好的一天
It's a fine day.
是嗎
Is it?
或許不是吧
Perhaps not.
正是  或許吧
Oh, indeed. Perhaps not.
或許塞勒姆將不會再有美好的明天
Perhaps there will be no more fine days in Salem.
或許美好時光已經離我們遠去
Perhaps the days of fine days are tragically behind us.
我有什么地方得罪你了嗎  霍爾小姐
Have I offended you, Miss Hale?
讓一個女人為你心存愛慕
Do you consider it offensive
而你的心卻另有所屬
raising hope in a heart most normally well-guarded
你覺得這是一種罪過嗎
while your own beats in the breast of another?
你覺得這種行為應受譴責嗎  奧登上尉
Do you, Captain Alden, find that reprehensible
-亦或只是無心之失  -這個  我
- or simply unkind? - Well, I...
還是你根本從未在意過這個問題
Or, most likely, you think not of it at all
或是我或是任何人  因為這就是男人的天性
or me or others, as is the wont and practice of most men.
西布里夫人
Ah, Mrs. Sibley.
安
Anne.
來得正是時候
Perfect.
你是否慶幸自己已不再年少無知
Are you ever grateful to be no longer young?
是的
Yes.
不過她的年少輕狂倒讓我想起了另一個人
Though her youthful moxie does bring to mind another.
我從未如此年少輕狂
I was never that young.
曾經  我們都是的
We were both...once.
你怎么會來集市
What brings you to market?
緹圖芭
Tituba.
我們約好在草藥師那見面
We were to meet at the herbalist.
這死亡之地倒挺適合你們倆的
A fine pair you two make in this place of death.
給她吧
Give it to her.
我需要時間
It will take time.
一旦你完成了立刻告訴我結果
And you will report to me as soon as you're finished.
不敢在此久留嗎
Afraid to stay?
我還有更有意義的事情要做
My time is better spent elsewhere.
這樣最好
For the best.
一個人只要沾染了黑暗之術
Once a man dabbles in the dark arts,
就很難再次回到光明
it's difficult for him to return to the light.
給我弄只兔子來
Fetch me a rabbit.
是的
Y-yes.
給我上去
Get on there!
西布里夫人
Mrs. Sibley.
布朗寧太太
Mrs. Browning.
別不好意思
Oh. No need to turn away.
他確實是個迷人的小伙
He is an arresting figure.
若不是我老眼昏花  我也會忍不住盯著他瞧呢
Only my old lady's eyes that keep me from staring myself.
別開玩笑了
Don't be ridiculous.
你還是不愿采納我的專業意見嗎
You still insist on ignoring my expertise.
沒錯
Yep.
我們可以用更專業
There are less pedestrian,
更和平的方式
less painful methods,
來達到我們的目的
with which we could accomplish our goals.
今晚一定要成功
It must happen tonight.
我們只有這一次機會
There will be no second chances.
普通人的法子對我來說就足夠了
The ways of the common are always good enough for me.
如果還能重創敵人  那就更好不過
And if it causes pain, so much the better.
看得出  她還在悶悶不樂
Still in a brown study, I see.
整天都沒說過一句話
Hasn't spoken a word all day.
她會好起來的
Mm. Well, she'll recover.
什么好起來
From what?
-你跟她說什么了  -沒什么
- What did you say to her? - Nothing.
只是想平復她內心不可避免的傷痛
Merely trying to spare her heart the inevitable woe.
不用擔心  親愛的
Worry not, my husband.
只要她成為柯頓·麥哲夫人
This will all be distant memory
這些就都只是遙遠的記憶了
Once she's become Mrs. Cotton Mather.
我在想
I wonder.
想什么
Wonder what?
如果他當初沒走  如果你當初可以嫁給他
If he'd never left, if you'd been allowed to marry,
如今與他成家立室
and found yourself now in that house of his
聽著小孩們無休止的哭鬧
with three squalling brats,
為了養家糊口無日無夜地工作
working ceaselessly to spread your meager wages...
奧登上尉對你還會有這么大吸引力嗎
Would Captain Alden still hold such desperate appeal?
還是你只是沉浸在一見鐘情的浪漫中
Or is it that you're trapped in first bliss,
刻骨銘心  無法自拔
romance from which there's no escape,
每當想起可能擁有的那一切
your heart ever hurting
便心痛得無以復加
from the imaginings of what could have been?
別在大庭廣眾下盯著他看  那會令你愈發軟弱
Do not stare at him in public. It weakens you.
你從來就沒想過吧
It never even occurs to you, does it?
我也許早就不需要你的至理名言了
I might have outgrown your sage advice.
盡管她無法開口
Though she cannot speak...
但她將指引我們找到巫師
...she will show us the witch!
她將指引我們找到巫師
She will show us the witch!
[咒語]
Balbin, gab, gabor, agaba!
復活吧  我召喚你
Arise, I call thee!
[咒語]
Colpriziana, offina alta nestra,
Fuaro menut.
威廉·霍克  你是我要尋找的死靈
William Hooke, thou art the dead I seek.
威廉·霍克  回應我的召喚
William Hooke, answer my calling.
她將指引我們找到巫師
She will show us the witch!
盡管她無法開口
Though she cannot speak...
她將指引我們找到巫師
...she will show us the witch!
She will show us the witch!
她將指引我們找到巫師
阻止她  牧師  她在讓你出丑
Stop her, reverend. She makes mockery of you.
快阻止她
Stop her!
威廉·霍克  你是我要尋找的死靈
William Hooke, thou art the dead I seek.
威廉·霍克  回應我的召喚
William hooke, answer my calling.
[咒語]  用力  呼吸
Fortis roa, strength and breath,
用力  呼吸  用力  呼吸
Strength and breath, strength and breath.
威廉·霍克  你是我要尋找的死靈
William Hooke, thou art the dead I seek.
威廉·霍克  回應我的召喚
William Hooke, answer my calling.
用力  呼吸  用力  呼吸  用力  呼吸
Strength and breath, strength and breath, strength and breath.
是你
You.
是我
Yes.
我還以為我們的買賣已經做完了
I thought our business concluded.
告訴我約翰·奧登的秘密
Tell me John Alden's secret.
到地獄來問我吧  婊子
Meet me in hell, you bitch.
有的地方可比地獄還糟
Oh, there are worse places than hell.
快說
Speak!
巫師
Witch!
天啊  艾米莉
Oh, no, Emily.
是你父親
It's your father.
怎么回事
What's happened now?
問你的主子去吧  我可不知道
Query your mistress. I haven't the faintest idea.
你的任務怎么樣了
What of your mission?
早該料到你在這里
Of course I find you here,
不去監獄里調查剛被指認出來的巫師
Not at the jail investigating this new witch,
不去查看梅西·路易絲
Not with Mercy Lewis,
倒是跑這兒來玩你那些天殺的玩具了
But here, alone, playing with your blasted toys.
看來我只能讓您不快了  西布里夫人
It seems I am determined to displease you, Mrs. Sibley.
西布里夫人
Mrs. Sibley.
別這樣
Please.
-抱歉  -請坐
- I'm sorry - Please.
告訴我  何事讓您如此煩心
Tell me... what troubles you.
那女孩已經迷失在權力之中
That girl has gone mad with power.
她受到同齡人的煽動  被不堪的爭論所影響
Encouraged by her peers, influenced by petty dispute.
行政委員們擔心她已經不再可靠了
The selectmen fear that she's no longer reliable.
胡說
Nonsense.
他們不確定是否還能信任她
They are uncertain that she can be further trusted.
這由不得他們決定
It is not theirs to decide.
我會對那女孩進行評估
I will assess the girl
決定她是否仍能勝任她的職責
and form my own opinion of her role.
你會這么做嗎  牧師
You would do that, reverend?
當然
Of course.
這許多的責任快將我壓垮了
I am torn and harried by my many responsibilities.
都是我的錯
It's my fault completely.
我沒考慮到這會給你帶來的負擔
I hadn't considered the toll this has taken on you.
在這種危急時刻  行政委員間的任何嫌隙
Oh, and a rift amongst the selectmen at this fragile moment
都可能成為我  或是塞勒姆  無法承擔的重負
might be more burden than I... or salem...could bear.
別擔心  西布里夫人
Worry not, Mrs. Sibley.
您召喚我前來主理這些巫師審訊
You fetched me here to run these witch trials,
我一定會盡我所能的
and run them I must.
謝謝你  牧師
Thank you, reverend.
知道至少還有一個人
What a relief to find
能分擔我的痛苦  真是太令人欣慰了
at least one who can relieve my hardships.
那是什么
What is that?
是一樣我正在研究的物件
It's an artifact that I'm researching.
和巫師有關嗎
Does it have to do with witches?
和大祭典有關
It's associated with the grand rite,
數個世紀以來屬于巫師的一種死亡儀式
a ritual of death attributed to witches over the centuries.
為什么這件物品讓你如此在意
And why does this object in particular concern you?
和巫師相關的所有事我都關心  夫人
Everything regarding witches concerns me, madam.
我們得做萬全準備
We cannot be too prepared.
看來您父親無暇前來對塞勒姆來說真是幸事
What luck for Salem that your father was unavailable.
小鎮的未來就仰仗你了  牧師
We will owe our future to you, reverend.
對此我十分確信
Of that I am sure.
那個秘密沒用
The secret is useless.
約翰·奧登可不會為了區區賭債而離開小鎮
John Alden will not leave town for a gambling debt.
她這么和你說的
That's what she told you?
她騙了我
She lied?
我會逼她說出真相的
I'll beat it out of her.
不需要
No.
難道緹圖芭不渴望大祭典嗎
Does Tituba not yearn for the grand rite?
事實上  還會有比她更渴望大祭典的人嗎
Is there another, in fact, that craves it more?
所以她會使用真正的秘密
So she'll use the real secret.
以她自己的方式  但是為了同樣的目的
In her own way, but for the same purpose --
來控制瑪麗
to control Mary.
另外還有個問題
We have another problem.
本該由威廉·霍克遞送的物件
The object William Hooke was tasked to deliver
現已落入旁人之手
has fallen into other hands.
威廉·霍克運送的到底是什么
And what exactly was William Hooke tasked to deliver?
惡靈
The Malum.
The Malum?
我們必須做好準備  應對每一種可能
We must be prepared for every eventuality,
即使沒有了瑪麗·西布里
even one that does not include Mary Sibley.
這就是惡靈的作用
That is the malum's purpose.
它在誰手里
Who has it?
約翰·奧登
John Alden.
我在集市里找你來著
I looked for you at market.
藥店的存貨不夠了
The apotek ran low.
我只得自己去采藥
I was forced to pick the bark myself.
再有一句謊話  這就會是你的臨終遺言
The next lie to cross your lips will be your last.
你竟然威脅我  你唯一真正的盟友
You would threaten me, your one true ally?
就是說其他人都已背叛我了
So the others have turned on me.
沒錯
Yes.
-誰  -每個人
- Who?  - Each and every one.
蘿絲
Rose?
每個人
Everyone.
他們私下見面
They meet in secret,
談論你的弱點
speak of your weakness,
謀劃著要把約翰·奧登趕出塞勒姆
plot to rid Salem of John Alden.
怕他會讓我迷失自我
Fearful he has taken me from myself.
沒錯
Yes.
一派胡言
Nonsense.
一切盡在我掌控之中
I am most completely myself!
你沒有
You are not!
你陷入了愛河
You are in love.
讓我告訴你關于他的事  這個你愛的男人
Let me tell you about him -- this man that you love.
他是個殺人犯
He is a murderer.
-他不是  -他是
- He is not. - Yes.
他剛剛才又殺了一人  來保守自己的秘密
And he has killed yet another to keep his secret.
如果我告訴治安官  民兵們就會前來
If I tell the magistrate, the militia will come,
逮捕他  并且絞死他
they will take him, and they will hang him.
你說謊
Lies.
如果你希望約翰·奧登活著
If you wish for John Alden to live,
你就必須完成大祭典
you will complete the grand rite.
下輪滿月之前必須再有八人死亡
The next moon will see eight more dead.
你說謊
Lies.
死人從不說謊
The dead don't lie.
父親  你好
Hello, father.
我被關起來了
I'm locked up.
沒錯
Yes, you are.
為什么
What for?
你是個巫師
You're a witch.
酒鬼  出老千  騙子這些可能沒錯
A drunk, a card sharp, a two-timer, maybe.
可巫師嗎
But a witch?
我可不認同
I think not.
我是來道別的
I come to say goodbye.
謝謝你"無微不至"的照顧
and thanks for nothing.
不用多久  我就會被釋放
I'll be out of here in no time,
然后跟之前說好的一樣  我會把你賣了
and then you will be sold, just like we planned.
或者你會被絞死
Or you'll hang...
或被燒死
Or burn.
我們走著瞧  父親
We'll see, father.
走著瞧
We'll see.
霍普金斯小姐
Miss Hopkins?
霍爾小姐
Miss -- miss Hale.
這點小心意用來幫你度過
A small collection to help ease your circumstances
這段難過的時期
in this most trying time.
謝謝你
Thank you.
他會得到公正的審判的
He'll get a fair trial.
我父親會確保這一點
My father will see to that,
不然我會確保他這么做
or I'll see to my father.
你真是善良  霍爾小姐
You're most kind, Miss Hale.
這不是出于善良
Ah, it's not kindness.
他們吊死了我的朋友
They hung my friend.
我看著她亂踢  尖叫
I watched her kick and...scream
然后
and...
尿了褲子
soil herself.
我不想再袖手旁觀了
I will not do that again.
保持堅強
Stay strong.
是說實話的時候了
Time for truth.
我之前對你撒謊了
I lied to you earlier.
我也年輕過
I was young once --
年輕到相信善良美德
young enough that I believed in goodness.
我相信是因為我在你身上看到了它們
I believed in it because I saw it in you.
這就是你  即使不刻意
You can't help it. Y-you can't stop it.
你身上仍充滿著這種品質
You can't be any other way.
我想這就是為什么我那時愛上了你
And I think that's why I loved you.
想想我有多震撼
Imagine my surprise...
當我聽到你是殺人犯的時候
being told you're a murderer.
你不了解我
You don't know me.
什么
What?
你不了解我
You don't know me!
-我殺了二十個人  -不
- I killed 20 men. - No.
沒錯  二十個人
Yes. 20 men.
而他們唯一的罪就是來救我
And their only crime was that they had come to save me.
不  我不相信
No, I won't believe it.
信不信都是真的
Believe it because it's true!
幸運之人至死不憾
Lucky men go to their graves with no regrets.
而我不曾一日無悔
Barely a day passes when I don't have one.
有時  我們不得不做出選擇
Sometimes in life, we make choices.
而這些艱難的選擇
And sometimes, these -- these difficult choices --
會促使我們做出一些事  可怕的事
they lead us to do things, terrible things,
即便有違我們本意
and we don't wish to.
我們盡力避免
We'd do anything not to.
但選擇孕育選擇
But choice informs choice.
有時候  你的行為
Your actions, though your own,
并不代表著
They -- they don't resemble
你任何的期許或是愿望
anything you'd have wanted or wished for.
告訴我你也是這樣的
Tell me that it was like that,
告訴我那是個艱難的選擇
Tell me that it was a difficult choice,
你無能為力  求你了  求你了
a terrible thing, please, please,
這樣我才能繼續相信善良美德
So that I might still believe in goodness.
我屠殺了二十個人
I murdered 20 men.
我不會為自己找任何借口
And I make no excuses for myself.
你會逮捕我嗎
Will you have me arrested?
我是唯一知情的人
I am the only one that knows.
黑暗之子  眾靈之主
Prince of darkness, master of all,
邪惡之父  聽吾之召
father of evil, hear our call.
黑暗之子  眾靈之主
Prince of darkness, master of all,
邪惡之父  聽吾之召  黑暗...
father of evil, hear our call. Prince...
...邪惡之父  聽吾之召
...father of evil, hear our call.
黑暗之子...
Prince of darkness...
...邪惡之父  聽吾之召
...father of evil, hear our call.
黑暗之子  眾靈之主
Prince of darkness, master of all,
邪惡之父  聽吾之召
father of evil, hear our call.
黑暗之子  眾靈之主...
Prince of darkness, master of all...
黑暗之子  眾靈之主
Prince of darkness, master of all,
邪惡之父  聽吾之召
father of evil, hear our call.
...邪惡之父  聽吾之召
...father of evil, hear our call!
黑暗之子  眾靈之主
Prince of darkness, master of all,
邪惡之父  聽吾之召
father of evil, hear our call.
黑暗之子  眾靈之主
Prince of darkness, master of all,
邪惡之父  聽吾之召
father of evil, hear our call!
黑暗之子  眾靈之主
Prince of darkness, master of all,
邪惡之父...
father of evil...
我們有過約定
We had a deal.
那項約定已經無法使我滿足
Our deal no longer pleases me.
那我再問一遍
Then I ask again --
你想要什么
what do you want?
我想變成和你一樣
I want to be just like you.